<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FofiFirstTime</string>
    <string name="top_guide_header">Guided first time Installation Setup</string>
    <string name="step1_subheader">Insert batteries in the remote control</string>
    <string name="step1_description">
        Your Fo-Fi ATV remote control comes with a pair of \n
        matched batteries of the proper size. Open the back \n
        cover of the remote control and insert the batteries,\n
        observing the correct polarity as indicated inside the \n
        battery compartment. \n\n

        Reattach the back cover.</string>
    <string name="step2_subheader">Add Pincode</string>
    <string name="step2_description">To make sure your ATV has all features available in your \n area/ locality, add the pincode where you are using the ATV.</string>
    <string name="step6_subheader">Add Pincode</string>
    <string name="step6_description">To make sure your ATV has all features available in your \n
area/ locality, add the pincode where you are using the ATV.</string>

    <string name="step3_subheader">Choose a Language</string>
    <string name="step3_description">
        When your Fo-Fi ATV powers on, the first screen will allow \n
you to choose a language. All text and dialog within the Fo- \n
Fi application will be displayed in the selected language. \n\n
Scroll up and down the list and press the button OK on your \n
Fo-Fi ATV remote to choose a language.</string>
    <string name="step4_subheader">Login to Fo-Fi account and activate your Fo-Fi ATV</string>
    <string name="step4_description">
        In order to activate your Fo-Fi ATV, it must be linked to a Fo- \n
Fi account. Your Fo-Fi account keeps track of which Fo-Fi \n
devices you own and allows you to add free and purchase \n
channels from the Fo-Fi Channel Store. \n\n
Instructions for activating your Fo-Fi ATV will be displayed \n
on your ATV, including an activation code; e.g. “ACV5T7”. \n\n
Note: Fo-Fi does NOT charge for device activation.</string>
    <string name="step5_subheader">Downloading the latest software</string>
    <string name="step5_description">
        Once connected to the internet, your Fo-Fi ATV will \n
download the latest version of Fo-Fi OS software and then \n
reboot.</string>
    <string name="check_net_connection">Kindly check your internet connection</string>
    <string name="setup_complete">Setup Complete</string>
    <string name="setup_complete_subheader">You’re now ready to start watching your favorite shows.</string>
    <string name="setup_complete_description">Tips: You can personalize your Fo-Fi ATV by changing your \n
theme or screensaver. You can use the Fo-Fi Channel Store \n
to add new streaming channels, games, themes, \n
screensavers, and other apps.</string>
    <string name="pincode_address_bangalore">Bengaluru, Karnataka \n
India</string>
</resources>
